[
  {
    "question": "ability",
    "word": "ability",
    "choices": [
      "能力",
      "小屋・別荘",
      "建築家",
      "仲間"
    ],
    "answer": "能力"
  },
  {
    "question": "abandon",
    "word": "abandon",
    "choices": [
      "連続した",
      "捕らえる",
      "捨てる",
      "大胆な"
    ],
    "answer": "捨てる"
  },
  {
    "question": "abrupt",
    "word": "abrupt",
    "choices": [
      "現れる",
      "現代の/同時代の",
      "評議会",
      "突然の"
    ],
    "answer": "突然の"
  },
  {
    "question": "absorb",
    "word": "absorb",
    "choices": [
      "生物学",
      "出来事",
      "構成する",
      "吸収する"
    ],
    "answer": "吸収する"
  },
  {
    "question": "abstract",
    "word": "abstract",
    "choices": [
      "借りる",
      "建設する",
      "抽象的な",
      "評議会"
    ],
    "answer": "抽象的な"
  },
  {
    "question": "abuse",
    "word": "abuse",
    "choices": [
      "乱用する",
      "結論づける",
      "引用する",
      "責める"
    ],
    "answer": "乱用する"
  },
  {
    "question": "accelerate",
    "word": "accelerate",
    "choices": [
      "突然の",
      "加速する",
      "任命する",
      "吸収する"
    ],
    "answer": "加速する"
  },
  {
    "question": "access",
    "word": "access",
    "choices": [
      "吸収する",
      "隠す",
      "許す",
      "接近・利用"
    ],
    "answer": "接近・利用"
  },
  {
    "question": "accident",
    "word": "accident",
    "choices": [
      "変える",
      "能力",
      "事故",
      "認める"
    ],
    "answer": "事故"
  },
  {
    "question": "accompany",
    "word": "accompany",
    "choices": [
      "構成する",
      "連続した",
      "相談する",
      "同行する"
    ],
    "answer": "同行する"
  },
  {
    "question": "accomplish",
    "word": "accomplish",
    "choices": [
      "構成要素",
      "結合する",
      "妥協する",
      "達成する"
    ],
    "answer": "達成する"
  },
  {
    "question": "account",
    "word": "account",
    "choices": [
      "心配して",
      "任命する",
      "説明・口座",
      "障壁"
    ],
    "answer": "説明・口座"
  },
  {
    "question": "accuse",
    "word": "accuse",
    "choices": [
      "雰囲気/大気",
      "大陸",
      "国境",
      "非難する"
    ],
    "answer": "非難する"
  },
  {
    "question": "achieve",
    "word": "achieve",
    "choices": [
      "達成する",
      "目が覚めて",
      "機関",
      "能力"
    ],
    "answer": "達成する"
  },
  {
    "question": "acquire",
    "word": "acquire",
    "choices": [
      "獲得する",
      "捨てる",
      "責める",
      "批判する"
    ],
    "answer": "獲得する"
  },
  {
    "question": "active",
    "word": "active",
    "choices": [
      "称賛する",
      "前進する",
      "構成要素",
      "積極的な"
    ],
    "answer": "積極的な"
  },
  {
    "question": "adapt",
    "word": "adapt",
    "choices": [
      "避ける",
      "何気ない",
      "適応する",
      "一定の"
    ],
    "answer": "適応する"
  },
  {
    "question": "addict",
    "word": "addict",
    "choices": [
      "中毒者",
      "承認する",
      "手配する",
      "驚くべき"
    ],
    "answer": "中毒者"
  },
  {
    "question": "adequate",
    "word": "adequate",
    "choices": [
      "十分な",
      "適応する",
      "命令する",
      "行政"
    ],
    "answer": "十分な"
  },
  {
    "question": "adjust",
    "word": "adjust",
    "choices": [
      "量",
      "調整する",
      "批評/コメント",
      "現れる"
    ],
    "answer": "調整する"
  },
  {
    "question": "administration",
    "word": "administration",
    "choices": [
      "気まずい",
      "気づいて",
      "保証する",
      "行政"
    ],
    "answer": "行政"
  },
  {
    "question": "admire",
    "word": "admire",
    "choices": [
      "任命する",
      "称賛する",
      "有能な",
      "攻撃的な"
    ],
    "answer": "称賛する"
  },
  {
    "question": "admit",
    "word": "admit",
    "choices": [
      "心配/関係",
      "賞",
      "認める",
      "大陸"
    ],
    "answer": "認める"
  },
  {
    "question": "adopt",
    "word": "adopt",
    "choices": [
      "均衡",
      "記事",
      "採用する/養子にする",
      "突然の"
    ],
    "answer": "採用する/養子にする"
  },
  {
    "question": "advance",
    "word": "advance",
    "choices": [
      "前進する",
      "確認する",
      "現代の/同時代の",
      "生き物"
    ],
    "answer": "前進する"
  },
  {
    "question": "advantage",
    "word": "advantage",
    "choices": [
      "衝突/故障",
      "評議会",
      "利点",
      "有能な"
    ],
    "answer": "利点"
  },
  {
    "question": "adventure",
    "word": "adventure",
    "choices": [
      "冒険",
      "保証する",
      "連続した",
      "認める"
    ],
    "answer": "冒険"
  },
  {
    "question": "advertisement",
    "word": "advertisement",
    "choices": [
      "到着",
      "説明・口座",
      "広告",
      "商業の"
    ],
    "answer": "広告"
  },
  {
    "question": "affair",
    "word": "affair",
    "choices": [
      "出来事",
      "能力/収容力",
      "仲間",
      "直面する"
    ],
    "answer": "出来事"
  },
  {
    "question": "affect",
    "word": "affect",
    "choices": [
      "意思疎通する",
      "企業の",
      "年1回の",
      "影響を与える"
    ],
    "answer": "影響を与える"
  },
  {
    "question": "afford",
    "word": "afford",
    "choices": [
      "行政",
      "余裕がある",
      "分析",
      "責める"
    ],
    "answer": "余裕がある"
  },
  {
    "question": "agency",
    "word": "agency",
    "choices": [
      "機関",
      "混乱させる",
      "資本/首都",
      "循環"
    ],
    "answer": "機関"
  },
  {
    "question": "agenda",
    "word": "agenda",
    "choices": [
      "議題",
      "加速する",
      "抽象的な",
      "犯す/委ねる"
    ],
    "answer": "議題"
  },
  {
    "question": "aggressive",
    "word": "aggressive",
    "choices": [
      "批評/コメント",
      "許す",
      "借りる",
      "攻撃的な"
    ],
    "answer": "攻撃的な"
  },
  {
    "question": "agriculture",
    "word": "agriculture",
    "choices": [
      "構成する/作曲する",
      "用心深い",
      "状況",
      "農業"
    ],
    "answer": "農業"
  },
  {
    "question": "aid",
    "word": "aid",
    "choices": [
      "企業の",
      "建築",
      "援助",
      "結合する"
    ],
    "answer": "援助"
  },
  {
    "question": "aim",
    "word": "aim",
    "choices": [
      "目が覚めて",
      "目的",
      "驚かす",
      "広告"
    ],
    "answer": "目的"
  },
  {
    "question": "alert",
    "word": "alert",
    "choices": [
      "用心深い",
      "生じる",
      "古代の",
      "祝う"
    ],
    "answer": "用心深い"
  },
  {
    "question": "alien",
    "word": "alien",
    "choices": [
      "観客",
      "仮定する",
      "異質の/外国の",
      "年1回の"
    ],
    "answer": "異質の/外国の"
  },
  {
    "question": "allege",
    "word": "allege",
    "choices": [
      "主張する",
      "都合のよい",
      "生じる",
      "障壁"
    ],
    "answer": "主張する"
  },
  {
    "question": "allow",
    "word": "allow",
    "choices": [
      "障壁",
      "接近・利用",
      "批評/コメント",
      "許す"
    ],
    "answer": "許す"
  },
  {
    "question": "alter",
    "word": "alter",
    "choices": [
      "計算する",
      "予算",
      "変える",
      "割り当てる"
    ],
    "answer": "変える"
  },
  {
    "question": "amazing",
    "word": "amazing",
    "choices": [
      "偏見",
      "結合する",
      "適切な",
      "驚くべき"
    ],
    "answer": "驚くべき"
  },
  {
    "question": "ambition",
    "word": "ambition",
    "choices": [
      "眠って",
      "承認する",
      "野心",
      "驚かす"
    ],
    "answer": "野心"
  },
  {
    "question": "amount",
    "word": "amount",
    "choices": [
      "報道",
      "量",
      "仲間",
      "加速する"
    ],
    "answer": "量"
  },
  {
    "question": "analysis",
    "word": "analysis",
    "choices": [
      "称賛する",
      "分析",
      "輝かしい",
      "割り当てる"
    ],
    "answer": "分析"
  },
  {
    "question": "ancestor",
    "word": "ancestor",
    "choices": [
      "属する",
      "同行する",
      "相談する",
      "祖先"
    ],
    "answer": "祖先"
  },
  {
    "question": "ancient",
    "word": "ancient",
    "choices": [
      "建築",
      "古代の",
      "批判する",
      "引きつける"
    ],
    "answer": "古代の"
  },
  {
    "question": "anger",
    "word": "anger",
    "choices": [
      "建築家",
      "小屋・別荘",
      "対比",
      "怒り"
    ],
    "answer": "怒り"
  },
  {
    "question": "annual",
    "word": "annual",
    "choices": [
      "確認する",
      "状況",
      "年1回の",
      "創造する"
    ],
    "answer": "年1回の"
  },
  {
    "question": "anxious",
    "word": "anxious",
    "choices": [
      "現れる",
      "同僚",
      "心配して",
      "主張する"
    ],
    "answer": "心配して"
  },
  {
    "question": "appeal",
    "word": "appeal",
    "choices": [
      "通貨",
      "突然の",
      "訴える",
      "集中する"
    ],
    "answer": "訴える"
  },
  {
    "question": "appear",
    "word": "appear",
    "choices": [
      "年1回の",
      "能力",
      "競争する",
      "現れる"
    ],
    "answer": "現れる"
  },
  {
    "question": "apparent",
    "word": "apparent",
    "choices": [
      "心配して",
      "明白な",
      "企業の",
      "隠す"
    ],
    "answer": "明白な"
  },
  {
    "question": "apply",
    "word": "apply",
    "choices": [
      "意識して",
      "申し込む/当てはまる",
      "結論づける",
      "批評/コメント"
    ],
    "answer": "申し込む/当てはまる"
  },
  {
    "question": "appoint",
    "word": "appoint",
    "choices": [
      "機関",
      "任命する",
      "文脈/状況",
      "気まずい"
    ],
    "answer": "任命する"
  },
  {
    "question": "appreciate",
    "word": "appreciate",
    "choices": [
      "借りる",
      "建築",
      "議題",
      "感謝する"
    ],
    "answer": "感謝する"
  },
  {
    "question": "appropriate",
    "word": "appropriate",
    "choices": [
      "循環",
      "前進する",
      "議題",
      "適切な"
    ],
    "answer": "適切な"
  },
  {
    "question": "approve",
    "word": "approve",
    "choices": [
      "達成する",
      "承認する",
      "試み",
      "会議"
    ],
    "answer": "承認する"
  },
  {
    "question": "architect",
    "word": "architect",
    "choices": [
      "国境",
      "建築家",
      "有能な",
      "意思疎通する"
    ],
    "answer": "建築家"
  },
  {
    "question": "architecture",
    "word": "architecture",
    "choices": [
      "偏見",
      "建築",
      "人工の",
      "主張する"
    ],
    "answer": "建築"
  },
  {
    "question": "argue",
    "word": "argue",
    "choices": [
      "避ける",
      "仮定する",
      "議論する",
      "驚かす"
    ],
    "answer": "議論する"
  },
  {
    "question": "arise",
    "word": "arise",
    "choices": [
      "消費する",
      "生じる",
      "達成する",
      "直面する"
    ],
    "answer": "生じる"
  },
  {
    "question": "arrange",
    "word": "arrange",
    "choices": [
      "広告",
      "大陸",
      "手配する",
      "都合のよい"
    ],
    "answer": "手配する"
  },
  {
    "question": "arrival",
    "word": "arrival",
    "choices": [
      "一致する/文通する",
      "国境",
      "達成する",
      "到着"
    ],
    "answer": "到着"
  },
  {
    "question": "article",
    "word": "article",
    "choices": [
      "生き物",
      "現代の/同時代の",
      "記事",
      "化学の"
    ],
    "answer": "記事"
  },
  {
    "question": "artificial",
    "word": "artificial",
    "choices": [
      "貢献する",
      "量",
      "事故",
      "人工の"
    ],
    "answer": "人工の"
  },
  {
    "question": "ashamed",
    "word": "ashamed",
    "choices": [
      "慈善",
      "恥じて",
      "中核",
      "文化"
    ],
    "answer": "恥じて"
  },
  {
    "question": "aspect",
    "word": "aspect",
    "choices": [
      "前進する",
      "建築家",
      "側面",
      "機関"
    ],
    "answer": "側面"
  },
  {
    "question": "asleep",
    "word": "asleep",
    "choices": [
      "現代の/同時代の",
      "眠って",
      "権威",
      "連続した"
    ],
    "answer": "眠って"
  },
  {
    "question": "asset",
    "word": "asset",
    "choices": [
      "含む",
      "資産",
      "論争の",
      "かなりの"
    ],
    "answer": "資産"
  },
  {
    "question": "assign",
    "word": "assign",
    "choices": [
      "地域社会",
      "眠って",
      "割り当てる",
      "試み"
    ],
    "answer": "割り当てる"
  },
  {
    "question": "assist",
    "word": "assist",
    "choices": [
      "承認する",
      "借りる",
      "国境",
      "助ける"
    ],
    "answer": "助ける"
  },
  {
    "question": "assume",
    "word": "assume",
    "choices": [
      "仮定する",
      "輝かしい",
      "有能な",
      "建設する"
    ],
    "answer": "仮定する"
  },
  {
    "question": "assure",
    "word": "assure",
    "choices": [
      "訴える",
      "怒り",
      "用心深い",
      "保証する"
    ],
    "answer": "保証する"
  },
  {
    "question": "astonish",
    "word": "astonish",
    "choices": [
      "利益",
      "状況",
      "驚かす",
      "気まずい"
    ],
    "answer": "驚かす"
  },
  {
    "question": "athlete",
    "word": "athlete",
    "choices": [
      "納得させる",
      "運動選手",
      "競争する",
      "文化"
    ],
    "answer": "運動選手"
  },
  {
    "question": "atmosphere",
    "word": "atmosphere",
    "choices": [
      "特徴",
      "挑戦",
      "妥協する",
      "雰囲気/大気"
    ],
    "answer": "雰囲気/大気"
  },
  {
    "question": "attempt",
    "word": "attempt",
    "choices": [
      "試み",
      "同行する",
      "怒り",
      "良心"
    ],
    "answer": "試み"
  },
  {
    "question": "attitude",
    "word": "attitude",
    "choices": [
      "引きつける",
      "主張する",
      "態度",
      "偏見"
    ],
    "answer": "態度"
  },
  {
    "question": "attract",
    "word": "attract",
    "choices": [
      "企業の",
      "計算する",
      "引きつける",
      "通貨"
    ],
    "answer": "引きつける"
  },
  {
    "question": "audience",
    "word": "audience",
    "choices": [
      "批判する",
      "祖先",
      "境界",
      "観客"
    ],
    "answer": "観客"
  },
  {
    "question": "authority",
    "word": "authority",
    "choices": [
      "消費する",
      "気まずい",
      "権威",
      "古代の"
    ],
    "answer": "権威"
  },
  {
    "question": "available",
    "word": "available",
    "choices": [
      "含む",
      "適応する",
      "利用できる",
      "競争する"
    ],
    "answer": "利用できる"
  },
  {
    "question": "average",
    "word": "average",
    "choices": [
      "平均の",
      "避ける",
      "建設する",
      "創造する"
    ],
    "answer": "平均の"
  },
  {
    "question": "avoid",
    "word": "avoid",
    "choices": [
      "態度",
      "接近・利用",
      "避ける",
      "感謝する"
    ],
    "answer": "避ける"
  },
  {
    "question": "awake",
    "word": "awake",
    "choices": [
      "観客",
      "文脈/状況",
      "目が覚めて",
      "生物学"
    ],
    "answer": "目が覚めて"
  },
  {
    "question": "award",
    "word": "award",
    "choices": [
      "賞",
      "驚くべき",
      "抽象的な",
      "計算する"
    ],
    "answer": "賞"
  },
  {
    "question": "aware",
    "word": "aware",
    "choices": [
      "複雑な",
      "競争する",
      "化学の",
      "気づいて"
    ],
    "answer": "気づいて"
  },
  {
    "question": "awkward",
    "word": "awkward",
    "choices": [
      "気まずい",
      "計算する",
      "資本/首都",
      "説明・口座"
    ],
    "answer": "気まずい"
  },
  {
    "question": "balance",
    "word": "balance",
    "choices": [
      "均衡",
      "小屋・別荘",
      "会議",
      "耕す/育む"
    ],
    "answer": "均衡"
  },
  {
    "question": "barrier",
    "word": "barrier",
    "choices": [
      "調整する",
      "通貨",
      "心配して",
      "障壁"
    ],
    "answer": "障壁"
  },
  {
    "question": "behave",
    "word": "behave",
    "choices": [
      "責める",
      "ふるまう",
      "かなりの",
      "犯す/委ねる"
    ],
    "answer": "ふるまう"
  },
  {
    "question": "belief",
    "word": "belief",
    "choices": [
      "信念",
      "前進する",
      "〜に加えて",
      "良心"
    ],
    "answer": "信念"
  },
  {
    "question": "belong",
    "word": "belong",
    "choices": [
      "属する",
      "分析",
      "実施する/導く",
      "含む"
    ],
    "answer": "属する"
  },
  {
    "question": "benefit",
    "word": "benefit",
    "choices": [
      "能力",
      "論争の",
      "目的",
      "利益"
    ],
    "answer": "利益"
  },
  {
    "question": "besides",
    "word": "besides",
    "choices": [
      "〜に加えて",
      "感謝する",
      "出来事",
      "事故"
    ],
    "answer": "〜に加えて"
  },
  {
    "question": "bias",
    "word": "bias",
    "choices": [
      "混沌",
      "偏見",
      "気づいて",
      "命令する"
    ],
    "answer": "偏見"
  },
  {
    "question": "bilingual",
    "word": "bilingual",
    "choices": [
      "挑戦",
      "バイリンガルの",
      "保護",
      "捕らえる"
    ],
    "answer": "バイリンガルの"
  },
  {
    "question": "biology",
    "word": "biology",
    "choices": [
      "生物学",
      "主張する",
      "乱用する",
      "認める"
    ],
    "answer": "生物学"
  },
  {
    "question": "blame",
    "word": "blame",
    "choices": [
      "捕らえる",
      "責める",
      "妥協する",
      "挑戦"
    ],
    "answer": "責める"
  },
  {
    "question": "bold",
    "word": "bold",
    "choices": [
      "集中する",
      "大胆な",
      "利用できる",
      "恥じて"
    ],
    "answer": "大胆な"
  },
  {
    "question": "border",
    "word": "border",
    "choices": [
      "崩壊する",
      "調整する",
      "国境",
      "観客"
    ],
    "answer": "国境"
  },
  {
    "question": "borrow",
    "word": "borrow",
    "choices": [
      "人工の",
      "挑戦",
      "借りる",
      "一致する/文通する"
    ],
    "answer": "借りる"
  },
  {
    "question": "boundary",
    "word": "boundary",
    "choices": [
      "変換する",
      "障壁",
      "快適さ",
      "境界"
    ],
    "answer": "境界"
  },
  {
    "question": "brilliant",
    "word": "brilliant",
    "choices": [
      "複雑な",
      "調整する",
      "輝かしい",
      "終わる/やめる"
    ],
    "answer": "輝かしい"
  },
  {
    "question": "broadcast",
    "word": "broadcast",
    "choices": [
      "影響を与える",
      "到着",
      "放送する",
      "議題"
    ],
    "answer": "放送する"
  },
  {
    "question": "budget",
    "word": "budget",
    "choices": [
      "予算",
      "達成する",
      "比較する",
      "確認する"
    ],
    "answer": "予算"
  },
  {
    "question": "candidate",
    "word": "candidate",
    "choices": [
      "仮定する",
      "候補者",
      "地域社会",
      "妥協する"
    ],
    "answer": "候補者"
  },
  {
    "question": "capacity",
    "word": "capacity",
    "choices": [
      "能力/収容力",
      "申し込む/当てはまる",
      "仮定する",
      "自信がある"
    ],
    "answer": "能力/収容力"
  },
  {
    "question": "capital",
    "word": "capital",
    "choices": [
      "議題",
      "承認する",
      "資本/首都",
      "納得させる"
    ],
    "answer": "資本/首都"
  },
  {
    "question": "capture",
    "word": "capture",
    "choices": [
      "変換する",
      "主張する",
      "捕らえる",
      "報道"
    ],
    "answer": "捕らえる"
  },
  {
    "question": "casual",
    "word": "casual",
    "choices": [
      "何気ない",
      "地域社会",
      "結論づける",
      "輝かしい"
    ],
    "answer": "何気ない"
  },
  {
    "question": "cease",
    "word": "cease",
    "choices": [
      "年1回の",
      "終わる/やめる",
      "直面する",
      "市民の/民間の"
    ],
    "answer": "終わる/やめる"
  },
  {
    "question": "challenge",
    "word": "challenge",
    "choices": [
      "挑戦",
      "商業の",
      "割り当てる",
      "突然の"
    ],
    "answer": "挑戦"
  },
  {
    "question": "chaos",
    "word": "chaos",
    "choices": [
      "犯す/委ねる",
      "十分な",
      "混沌",
      "対比"
    ],
    "answer": "混沌"
  },
  {
    "question": "characteristic",
    "word": "characteristic",
    "choices": [
      "助ける",
      "特徴",
      "候補者",
      "達成する"
    ],
    "answer": "特徴"
  },
  {
    "question": "charity",
    "word": "charity",
    "choices": [
      "能力/収容力",
      "均衡",
      "慈善",
      "議題"
    ],
    "answer": "慈善"
  },
  {
    "question": "chemical",
    "word": "chemical",
    "choices": [
      "混沌",
      "申し込む/当てはまる",
      "祖先",
      "化学の"
    ],
    "answer": "化学の"
  },
  {
    "question": "circumstance",
    "word": "circumstance",
    "choices": [
      "耕す/育む",
      "商品",
      "状況",
      "かなりの"
    ],
    "answer": "状況"
  },
  {
    "question": "cite",
    "word": "cite",
    "choices": [
      "引用する",
      "年1回の",
      "対立",
      "大陸"
    ],
    "answer": "引用する"
  },
  {
    "question": "civil",
    "word": "civil",
    "choices": [
      "市民の/民間の",
      "積極的な",
      "確認する",
      "偏見"
    ],
    "answer": "市民の/民間の"
  },
  {
    "question": "collapse",
    "word": "collapse",
    "choices": [
      "崩壊する",
      "能力/収容力",
      "報道",
      "意思疎通する"
    ],
    "answer": "崩壊する"
  },
  {
    "question": "colleague",
    "word": "colleague",
    "choices": [
      "同僚",
      "議論する",
      "十分な",
      "批評/コメント"
    ],
    "answer": "同僚"
  },
  {
    "question": "combine",
    "word": "combine",
    "choices": [
      "反対の/カウンター",
      "競争する",
      "一貫した",
      "結合する"
    ],
    "answer": "結合する"
  },
  {
    "question": "comfort",
    "word": "comfort",
    "choices": [
      "快適さ",
      "借りる",
      "保証する",
      "競争する"
    ],
    "answer": "快適さ"
  },
  {
    "question": "command",
    "word": "command",
    "choices": [
      "意識して",
      "命令する",
      "一致する/文通する",
      "突然の"
    ],
    "answer": "命令する"
  },
  {
    "question": "comment",
    "word": "comment",
    "choices": [
      "助ける",
      "会議",
      "予算",
      "批評/コメント"
    ],
    "answer": "批評/コメント"
  },
  {
    "question": "commercial",
    "word": "commercial",
    "choices": [
      "商業の",
      "偏見",
      "調整する",
      "接近・利用"
    ],
    "answer": "商業の"
  },
  {
    "question": "commit",
    "word": "commit",
    "choices": [
      "対立",
      "加速する",
      "犯す/委ねる",
      "責める"
    ],
    "answer": "犯す/委ねる"
  },
  {
    "question": "commodity",
    "word": "commodity",
    "choices": [
      "商品",
      "変える",
      "報道",
      "権威"
    ],
    "answer": "商品"
  },
  {
    "question": "communicate",
    "word": "communicate",
    "choices": [
      "商品",
      "対立",
      "心配/関係",
      "意思疎通する"
    ],
    "answer": "意思疎通する"
  },
  {
    "question": "community",
    "word": "community",
    "choices": [
      "接近・利用",
      "地域社会",
      "助ける",
      "非難する"
    ],
    "answer": "地域社会"
  },
  {
    "question": "companion",
    "word": "companion",
    "choices": [
      "気づいて",
      "結合する",
      "仲間",
      "会議"
    ],
    "answer": "仲間"
  },
  {
    "question": "compare",
    "word": "compare",
    "choices": [
      "実施する/導く",
      "比較する",
      "借りる",
      "商業の"
    ],
    "answer": "比較する"
  },
  {
    "question": "compete",
    "word": "compete",
    "choices": [
      "競争する",
      "気づいて",
      "祖先",
      "衝突/故障"
    ],
    "answer": "競争する"
  },
  {
    "question": "competent",
    "word": "competent",
    "choices": [
      "衝突/故障",
      "有能な",
      "手配する",
      "議論する"
    ],
    "answer": "有能な"
  },
  {
    "question": "complain",
    "word": "complain",
    "choices": [
      "変える",
      "前進する",
      "不平を言う",
      "側面"
    ],
    "answer": "不平を言う"
  },
  {
    "question": "complex",
    "word": "complex",
    "choices": [
      "複雑な",
      "連続した",
      "引用する",
      "気づいて"
    ],
    "answer": "複雑な"
  },
  {
    "question": "component",
    "word": "component",
    "choices": [
      "構成要素",
      "市民の/民間の",
      "祝う",
      "直面する"
    ],
    "answer": "構成要素"
  },
  {
    "question": "compose",
    "word": "compose",
    "choices": [
      "驚かす",
      "余裕がある",
      "隠す",
      "構成する/作曲する"
    ],
    "answer": "構成する/作曲する"
  },
  {
    "question": "compromise",
    "word": "compromise",
    "choices": [
      "妥協する",
      "年1回の",
      "利益",
      "現れる"
    ],
    "answer": "妥協する"
  },
  {
    "question": "compute",
    "word": "compute",
    "choices": [
      "計算する",
      "確認する",
      "同行する",
      "文化"
    ],
    "answer": "計算する"
  },
  {
    "question": "conceal",
    "word": "conceal",
    "choices": [
      "吸収する",
      "隠す",
      "眠って",
      "同行する"
    ],
    "answer": "隠す"
  },
  {
    "question": "concentrate",
    "word": "concentrate",
    "choices": [
      "農業",
      "計算する",
      "集中する",
      "気づいて"
    ],
    "answer": "集中する"
  },
  {
    "question": "concept",
    "word": "concept",
    "choices": [
      "自信がある",
      "利益",
      "野心",
      "概念"
    ],
    "answer": "概念"
  },
  {
    "question": "concern",
    "word": "concern",
    "choices": [
      "乱用する",
      "文脈/状況",
      "非難する",
      "心配/関係"
    ],
    "answer": "心配/関係"
  },
  {
    "question": "conclude",
    "word": "conclude",
    "choices": [
      "循環",
      "批評/コメント",
      "結論づける",
      "捨てる"
    ],
    "answer": "結論づける"
  },
  {
    "question": "concrete",
    "word": "concrete",
    "choices": [
      "抽象的な",
      "混沌",
      "具体的な",
      "変える"
    ],
    "answer": "具体的な"
  },
  {
    "question": "condemn",
    "word": "condemn",
    "choices": [
      "非難する",
      "仲間",
      "獲得する",
      "主張する"
    ],
    "answer": "非難する"
  },
  {
    "question": "conduct",
    "word": "conduct",
    "choices": [
      "実施する/導く",
      "都合のよい",
      "訴える",
      "混乱させる"
    ],
    "answer": "実施する/導く"
  },
  {
    "question": "conference",
    "word": "conference",
    "choices": [
      "積極的な",
      "会議",
      "雰囲気/大気",
      "機関"
    ],
    "answer": "会議"
  },
  {
    "question": "confident",
    "word": "confident",
    "choices": [
      "偏見",
      "よく考える",
      "自信がある",
      "かなりの"
    ],
    "answer": "自信がある"
  },
  {
    "question": "confirm",
    "word": "confirm",
    "choices": [
      "中毒者",
      "企業の",
      "確認する",
      "運動選手"
    ],
    "answer": "確認する"
  },
  {
    "question": "conflict",
    "word": "conflict",
    "choices": [
      "出来事",
      "驚かす",
      "対立",
      "雰囲気/大気"
    ],
    "answer": "対立"
  },
  {
    "question": "confront",
    "word": "confront",
    "choices": [
      "援助",
      "よく考える",
      "直面する",
      "十分な"
    ],
    "answer": "直面する"
  },
  {
    "question": "confuse",
    "word": "confuse",
    "choices": [
      "眠って",
      "混乱させる",
      "結合する",
      "祝う"
    ],
    "answer": "混乱させる"
  },
  {
    "question": "congratulate",
    "word": "congratulate",
    "choices": [
      "目的",
      "信念",
      "祝う",
      "〜に加えて"
    ],
    "answer": "祝う"
  },
  {
    "question": "conscience",
    "word": "conscience",
    "choices": [
      "不平を言う",
      "良心",
      "援助",
      "変換する"
    ],
    "answer": "良心"
  },
  {
    "question": "conscious",
    "word": "conscious",
    "choices": [
      "意識して",
      "責める",
      "事故",
      "現代の/同時代の"
    ],
    "answer": "意識して"
  },
  {
    "question": "consecutive",
    "word": "consecutive",
    "choices": [
      "比較する",
      "連続した",
      "非難する",
      "雰囲気/大気"
    ],
    "answer": "連続した"
  },
  {
    "question": "conservation",
    "word": "conservation",
    "choices": [
      "積極的な",
      "行政",
      "非難する",
      "保護"
    ],
    "answer": "保護"
  },
  {
    "question": "consider",
    "word": "consider",
    "choices": [
      "よく考える",
      "変える",
      "中毒者",
      "広告"
    ],
    "answer": "よく考える"
  },
  {
    "question": "considerable",
    "word": "considerable",
    "choices": [
      "かなりの",
      "攻撃的な",
      "野心",
      "変える"
    ],
    "answer": "かなりの"
  },
  {
    "question": "consistent",
    "word": "consistent",
    "choices": [
      "小屋・別荘",
      "一貫した",
      "納得させる",
      "生き物"
    ],
    "answer": "一貫した"
  },
  {
    "question": "constant",
    "word": "constant",
    "choices": [
      "仲間",
      "生き物",
      "一定の",
      "複雑な"
    ],
    "answer": "一定の"
  },
  {
    "question": "constitute",
    "word": "constitute",
    "choices": [
      "議題",
      "怒り",
      "構成する",
      "非難する"
    ],
    "answer": "構成する"
  },
  {
    "question": "construct",
    "word": "construct",
    "choices": [
      "地域社会",
      "建設する",
      "承認する",
      "慈善"
    ],
    "answer": "建設する"
  },
  {
    "question": "consult",
    "word": "consult",
    "choices": [
      "加速する",
      "相談する",
      "調整する",
      "事故"
    ],
    "answer": "相談する"
  },
  {
    "question": "consume",
    "word": "consume",
    "choices": [
      "中毒者",
      "現れる",
      "消費する",
      "実施する/導く"
    ],
    "answer": "消費する"
  },
  {
    "question": "contain",
    "word": "contain",
    "choices": [
      "現代の/同時代の",
      "含む",
      "循環",
      "採用する/養子にする"
    ],
    "answer": "含む"
  },
  {
    "question": "contemporary",
    "word": "contemporary",
    "choices": [
      "現代の/同時代の",
      "援助",
      "余裕がある",
      "納得させる"
    ],
    "answer": "現代の/同時代の"
  },
  {
    "question": "contend",
    "word": "contend",
    "choices": [
      "具体的な",
      "建築家",
      "ふるまう",
      "主張する/争う"
    ],
    "answer": "主張する/争う"
  },
  {
    "question": "context",
    "word": "context",
    "choices": [
      "文脈/状況",
      "手配する",
      "候補者",
      "生き物"
    ],
    "answer": "文脈/状況"
  },
  {
    "question": "continent",
    "word": "continent",
    "choices": [
      "建設する",
      "大陸",
      "運動選手",
      "報道"
    ],
    "answer": "大陸"
  },
  {
    "question": "contrast",
    "word": "contrast",
    "choices": [
      "構成する",
      "概念",
      "対比",
      "出来事"
    ],
    "answer": "対比"
  },
  {
    "question": "contribute",
    "word": "contribute",
    "choices": [
      "貢献する",
      "獲得する",
      "偏見",
      "企業の"
    ],
    "answer": "貢献する"
  },
  {
    "question": "controversial",
    "word": "controversial",
    "choices": [
      "出来事",
      "捕らえる",
      "論争の",
      "一貫した"
    ],
    "answer": "論争の"
  },
  {
    "question": "convenient",
    "word": "convenient",
    "choices": [
      "候補者",
      "都合のよい",
      "通貨",
      "達成する"
    ],
    "answer": "都合のよい"
  },
  {
    "question": "convert",
    "word": "convert",
    "choices": [
      "放送する",
      "変換する",
      "気づいて",
      "申し込む/当てはまる"
    ],
    "answer": "変換する"
  },
  {
    "question": "convince",
    "word": "convince",
    "choices": [
      "結合する",
      "心配して",
      "耕す/育む",
      "納得させる"
    ],
    "answer": "納得させる"
  },
  {
    "question": "cooperate",
    "word": "cooperate",
    "choices": [
      "一致する/文通する",
      "協力する",
      "候補者",
      "予算"
    ],
    "answer": "協力する"
  },
  {
    "question": "coordinate",
    "word": "coordinate",
    "choices": [
      "変える",
      "信念",
      "用心深い",
      "調整する"
    ],
    "answer": "調整する"
  },
  {
    "question": "core",
    "word": "core",
    "choices": [
      "会議",
      "称賛する",
      "中核",
      "良心"
    ],
    "answer": "中核"
  },
  {
    "question": "corporate",
    "word": "corporate",
    "choices": [
      "意識して",
      "説明・口座",
      "自信がある",
      "企業の"
    ],
    "answer": "企業の"
  },
  {
    "question": "correspond",
    "word": "correspond",
    "choices": [
      "一致する/文通する",
      "手配する",
      "乱用する",
      "有能な"
    ],
    "answer": "一致する/文通する"
  },
  {
    "question": "cottage",
    "word": "cottage",
    "choices": [
      "小屋・別荘",
      "援助",
      "用心深い",
      "異質の/外国の"
    ],
    "answer": "小屋・別荘"
  },
  {
    "question": "council",
    "word": "council",
    "choices": [
      "祖先",
      "利益",
      "商品",
      "評議会"
    ],
    "answer": "評議会"
  },
  {
    "question": "counter",
    "word": "counter",
    "choices": [
      "運動選手",
      "反対の/カウンター",
      "異質の/外国の",
      "余裕がある"
    ],
    "answer": "反対の/カウンター"
  },
  {
    "question": "courage",
    "word": "courage",
    "choices": [
      "生物学",
      "勇気",
      "地域社会",
      "バイリンガルの"
    ],
    "answer": "勇気"
  },
  {
    "question": "coverage",
    "word": "coverage",
    "choices": [
      "消費する",
      "評議会",
      "報道",
      "小屋・別荘"
    ],
    "answer": "報道"
  },
  {
    "question": "crash",
    "word": "crash",
    "choices": [
      "異質の/外国の",
      "衝突/故障",
      "構成する/作曲する",
      "不平を言う"
    ],
    "answer": "衝突/故障"
  },
  {
    "question": "create",
    "word": "create",
    "choices": [
      "創造する",
      "構成する",
      "同行する",
      "快適さ"
    ],
    "answer": "創造する"
  },
  {
    "question": "creature",
    "word": "creature",
    "choices": [
      "生き物",
      "一致する/文通する",
      "達成する",
      "資本/首都"
    ],
    "answer": "生き物"
  },
  {
    "question": "criticize",
    "word": "criticize",
    "choices": [
      "商業の",
      "議題",
      "批判する",
      "前進する"
    ],
    "answer": "批判する"
  },
  {
    "question": "crucial",
    "word": "crucial",
    "choices": [
      "重大な",
      "心配して",
      "調整する",
      "適切な"
    ],
    "answer": "重大な"
  },
  {
    "question": "cultivate",
    "word": "cultivate",
    "choices": [
      "調整する",
      "責める",
      "耕す/育む",
      "消費する"
    ],
    "answer": "耕す/育む"
  },
  {
    "question": "culture",
    "word": "culture",
    "choices": [
      "記事",
      "慈善",
      "文化",
      "障壁"
    ],
    "answer": "文化"
  },
  {
    "question": "currency",
    "word": "currency",
    "choices": [
      "国境",
      "怒り",
      "納得させる",
      "通貨"
    ],
    "answer": "通貨"
  },
  {
    "question": "cycle",
    "word": "cycle",
    "choices": [
      "一致する/文通する",
      "循環",
      "生き物",
      "現代の/同時代の"
    ],
    "answer": "循環"
  }
]